I'm home.
Welcome home, Akane.
You've been working so much
overtime lately. Are you all right?
Akane!
Momma!
It's all right. Momma's here.
Here, let me wipe you down.
There we go.
Yay!
What? She overworked herself into such a high fever
that she's regressed to infancy?
Yes.
Mother, how does one repair a human?
Well, you should probably give
her some medicine and let her rest.
Now that you've taken your
medicine, it's time for bed.
I don't wanna! I'm not sleepy!
I wanna stay up and talk!
Naked story time!
Hey, hey, Momma! Do you love me?
Of course I do. More than anyone in the world.
Really?
Akane loves you too.
Huh?
Why are my boobies so big all of a sudden?
Yours are huge too, Momma.
You can touch them if you like.
Really?
Wow, they're so soft.
Why stop at touching?
You can suck on them too.
No!
I'm not gonna drink Momma's milk!
I'm not a baby anymore! I'm a...
I'm a... I'm a...
Wait.
What am I?
That's right.
I caught a cold, so I've been with Momma all day.
Yeah.
Just me and Momma...
Nadeshiko?
What a relief.
I'm so sorry for all the trouble.
It sounds like your mother
was a very kind woman, Akane.
She must have doted on you for a long time,
and she clearly loved you very much.
I could never take the place of a mother like that.
Nah, she wasn't like that.
My mom would've just told me to sleep it off.
She wasn't the caregiving type.
That's why...
I'm glad you were here for me, Nadeshiko.
Thank you.
So, Nadeshiko,
about the whole master registration thing...
I'm still conflicted about treating you like an object,
but I promise I'll find a way
to go through with it someday.
So if you can just be patient
with me until then, I'd appreciate it.
Sure.
I'll just have to keep honing my sex skills
until that day comes.
Huh?
You and me...
we're going to do so much together.
Yeah, I'll...
need time to think about it.